dropsend.com 2017-05-10

# Privacy Policy | Send Large Files and Email Large Files

## Privacy Statement

DropSend is committed to protecting your privacy and maintaining the security of any personal information received from you. We strictly adhere to the requirements of the data protection legislation in the UK. The purpose of this statement is to explain to you what personal information we collect and how we may use it.  

  1. When you order, we need to know your name, address, email address and card details. This allows us to process and fulfill your order. You have the option to withhold personal information that is not required for the order process.

  2. We use your personal information solely for payment and billing purposes. We will only contact you with your consent.

  3. We do not sell, rent or exchange your personal information with any third party for commercial reasons, beyond the essential requirement for credit/debit card validation during purchase.

  4. We follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information which you have given us, to prevent DropSend access in accordance with the UK data protection legislation.

We do not collect sensitive information about you except when you specifically knowingly provide it. In order to maintain the accuracy of our database, you can check, update or remove your personal details by contacting us at [happytohelp@dropsend.com](mailto:happytohelp@dropsend.com) .

We use a technology called "cookies" as part of a normal business procedure to track patterns of behavior of visitors to our site. A cookie is an element of data that our Website sends to your browser which is then stored on your system. You can set your browser to prevent this happening. Any information collected in this way can be used to identify you unless you change your browser settings.  

  5. In order to process credit/debit card transactions, the bank or card processing agency may require verifying your personal details for authorization outside the EEA (European Economic Area). Your information will not be transferred outside the EEA for any other purpose.  

  6. As a registered user you agree to receive DropSend newsletters, product offers, promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. At any time you may decide to opt out and no longer receive such communications from us. Simply follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in our communications or email us at: happytohelp@dropsend.com with your written request to be removed from our mailing list.   

  7. If you have any questions about privacy please contact us at [happytohelp@dropsend.com](mailto:happytohelp@dropsend.com) .
